《Baremo》
《Baremo》が生まれた時から 男人話の主人公なのさ
出逢いや別れ繰り返し
この世界が幻でもいい
人生はまるでファンタジア
人生はきっとファンタシア 僕らの想像がいつの日か未来を変えてゆくのさ
拍手をして僕らを讃える
どうせなら楽しんでやれ
人生はまるでファンタジア
人生はきっとファンタシア 僕らの想像がいつの日か誰かを笑顔にするはず
人生はきっとファンタシア 僕らの想像がいつの日か未来を変えてゆくのさ
未来を変えてゆくのさ
Life is like Fantasy
歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・
歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞 歌詞、歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞、歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞・歌詞と歌詞・歌詞と歌詞と
I'll melt into the sky
Even though everyone lives such fleeting lives
Wherever this planet is, there is a struggle today
Look, the night sky shines
The petals are flying up
I want to burn your happy face
Even if it's a momentary illusion
A boy who was with me hundreds of years ago
Is surely a girl like you
And will fall in love again
Even if the world ends
We will never forget
The days I lived with you
And the way you looked at me
Even if it's a momentary dream
The joy of loving each other
The heart of forgiving each other
Will it reach the future?
Look, the night sky shines
The petals are flying up
I want to burn your happy face
Even if it's a momentary illusion
The heart of forgiving each other
I won't let go of your hand
Hold me tight
Translated by Releska
The weak heart that I've accumulated for a long time
Has become a mountain
The higher it goes, the more it reaches the atmosphere
I can't see it anymore
All of that, break it down
I'll go on a trip again
Are we still dreaming?
I'm looking for the best partner
Who I've never seen before
I cried and laughed
I'm aiming for the treasure of hope
On rainy days and rainy days
I'll sing the song of adventure
Translated by Releska
If you can't move by lining up the excuses and excuses
I'll leave you
I don't have time to regret
I'll go on a trip again
Are we still dreaming?
I'm looking for the best partner
Who I've never seen before
I cried and laughed
I'm aiming for the treasure of hope
Tonight
Are we still dreaming?
I'm looking for the best partner
Who I've never seen before
I cried and laughed
I'm aiming for the treasure of hope
On rainy days and rainy days
I'll sing the song of adventure
I'll go on a trip again
Are we still dreaming?
I'm looking for the best partner
Who I've never seen before
I cried and laughed
I'm looking for the best partner
Shouji, it's so wide
It was wider than I thought
Everyone
What should I call that area?
Is it a stand?
Stop the season in the sun
I can hear you a little late
Is that so?
But is it going to be three times?
It's going to be three times
Thank you for sending us so much love today
Thank you
Today is December 25th
It's Christmas
Are you going on a date?
Are you here to see Shouji Santa?
I'm here to see Yoji Tonakai
He's a big fan of Hire Carol
Thank you for giving us this day
on Christmas, December 25th
at the live performance of Narita Tomo Simpson's Yakanobuntai
We're so glad you gave us this day
We're going to send you a lot of love
Today is a live broadcast
It's already broadcasted
Please turn to the camera
Where is the camera?
Is it here?
Thank you for watching the live broadcast
It's December 25th
It's a very precious day
Thank you for watching the live broadcast
We're receiving your love
Shouji is very smooth today
He's talking
I'm going to put some honey on it
Today is our tour final
We have a wonderful guest
He's going to be our Christmas present
Thank you for watching until the end
We, Narita Tomo Simpson, released our second album, Fantasia, on November 29th
Did you hear that?
Please give a round of applause
It's been heard all over the world
Wait, let's do it again
We released our second album, Fantasia, on November 20th
Did you hear that?
Shouji, we're like the most popular group
It feels good
It feels like I'm dreaming
Today, we're going to listen to Shouji's song
Let's hear it
We're going to play it, One Way
One Way
I've been trying to figure it out
I can't reset it
It's a reality
Dreams are magic
I'm stopping my feet
I don't believe in you
It doesn't start, going one way
I'm drawing in the transparent rain
I'm losing it
I can't fix my brilliant childhood dream
When I forget, I remember
I've been living it somehow
I'm trying to figure it out
I'm losing it
I can't fix my brilliant childhood dream
When I forget, I remember
I'm losing it
I can't fix my brilliant childhood dream
When I forget, I remember
I've been trying to figure it out
I can't reset it
It's a reality
Dreams are magic
I'm stopping my feet
I don't believe in you
It doesn't start, going one way
I'm drawing in the transparent rain
I don't believe in you
It doesn't start, going one way
Thank you
It's going to ring
Now, it's time for Christmas
Shall we start the song?
It's suddenly started
Another song from the FANTASIA
I'll sing GOODBYE
Christmas Song
A city with a glass-glassed, shining city
A Christmas song from the radio
I gently throw it away at the end of love
I muttered, it's so sad
The love-pushing, even the lies
Ah, at midnight, the fantasy melts
Under the snow dyed in neon
I wait for spring forever
Counting my fingers, the light is on
It's strong, but I can't turn back
Now, I'll sing GOODBYE to you
Your dream, many times
Christmas rose on the window
If I close my eyes, I'll surely feel proud
It's painful not to wake up
Is it the answer to the love's goodbye?
Ah, the more I reach out, the more I see the blue bird
Under the moonlight, I wait for morning forever
Counting my fingers, the light is on
It's strong, but I can't turn back
Now, I'll sing GOODBYE to you
The love-pushing, even the lies
Ah, at midnight, the fantasy melts
Under the snow dyed in neon
I wait for spring forever
Counting my fingers, the light is on
It's strong, but I can't turn back
Now, I'll sing GOODBYE to you
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
I don't want to be kind anymore
I see you with a tired face
While reflecting his distant face in my eyes
I saw you smiling beside him for a long time
I understand the words you want
I don't mind if it's unfair
Don't get lost, come here
Come into my heart
Don't forget, it's okay
Now, rest your wings
Let's hold each other tight until we remember everything
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
He's already in love with someone else
He knows a new life
It's okay now, you say it
But you're still in my heart
Don't get lost, come here
Throw away everything
I'll wipe away your tears
And make you smile
I'll wait forever
Until the day we remember everything
Don't get lost, come here
Come into my heart
Don't get lost, just look straight at me
Let's hold each other tight until we remember everything
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
Without saying goodbye, only time passes
I'm drawn to the words that are swallowed by tears
Someday, I'm sure I'll be able to look up at the blue sky with a smile
I bite down on it while I believe
I'll cross yesterday's small wishes and go to tomorrow
I won't erase the big mistakes and mistakes
If life is a path of hope
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
Without answering, I wait for dawn
I'm falling apart, I'm looking at regret
I'm digging my pockets, what kind of face will I make now?
I bite down on it while I touch it
I'll cross yesterday's small wishes and go to tomorrow
I won't forget the big fights and betrayals
If life is a path of hope
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
I'll cross yesterday's small wishes and go to tomorrow
I won't erase the big mistakes and mistakes
I won't erase the small peace and prayers
I won't forget the big fights and betrayals
If life is a path of hope
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
Big Band Beef
One, two, one, two, three, four
The Love-Pushing, Even the Lies
Look at the crying kids, they laugh when they notice
No matter where in the world, it will reach in an instant
The beginning of a show with a mysterious power
The bass is shaking when the drums and I play the rhythm
When I ring the guitar, I'll sing with a voice
Big Band Girls, I'll make a beat
Look at the worried adults, they remember those days
If I can get a little courage, I can be anything
Tonight, I'll start the show on the stage of Yokohama
The drums and I play the rhythm
The bass is shaking when the drums and I play the rhythm
When I ring the guitar, I'll sing with a voice
Big Band Girls, I'll make a beat
The beginning of a show with a mysterious power
The drums and I play the rhythm
The bass is shaking when the drums and I play the beat
When I ring the guitar, I'll sing with a voice
Big Band Girls, I'll make a beat
Big Band We will play!
Please say, what?
Too fast?
Narita Thomas Simpson is a summer band
Hideki, Shoji and I met on the surf
We are a summer band
We only play in summer, we don't play in winter
Shoji is also in the sea for two thirds of a year
Of course, I came here by swimming
You came by taxi
I went by taxi to the sea and swam
I still have a wet suit on
Yes, we only play in summer
Please listen to Narita Thomas Simpson's summer song
Stop the season in the sun
Please take my heart
I want to stay like this forever
Stop the season, You’re my dream
Don't pass by the south wind
I can't do it, my feelings feel so blue
Big Band Girls, I'll make a beat
Wait, wait
That's a song for people, Shoji
You play live every year at Yokohama Stadium in Kannai
It's a summer band
Please play our representative song
I said I like you in the middle of the night
I took you into my dreams
I can't forget the blue sky
I can't become your voice
Stop the season in the sun
Where does the wave go?
Love & Love that passes by
Love is as it is
Wait, wait, wait
It's a super band that Kanagawa created
I've been doing this for a long time
But today is the day of the aurora
It's Christmas
I said I only play summer songs
But this is our first Christmas song
I felt like I could hold hands forever
Everything was shining
Stop the season, You’re my dream
I was afraid that you would disappear
I realized that I love people
Merry Christmas someday
Yokohama Stadium
Yokohama!
We're going to introduce our best teammates
Are you ready?
Takahashi Kazuya, Maeda Toyo, Okamoto Genji
Yokohama!
We are Rock On!
Yokohama Stadium
I still smell the scent of the mist
When I close my eyes, I feel the scent of citrus
The smell of the citrus
The taste of the water that flows through my wet body
Was that an illusion?
You're not here anymore
Ever since the history took you away
No one could love you more than that
The waves are coming to me
I want to hold you
Your long hair fluttering in the wind
The twilight of summer
Your skin is dyed orange
I wanted to drown with you
Before the magic of summer melts
Yokohama!
Can you hear me?
Hey!
Yokohama!
I'll introduce you again.
Kazuya Takahashi!
Koyo Maeda!
Keiichi Okamoto!
Please do that.
Kazuya.
We are.
Alright!
We are...
Kazuya!
We are!
Shoji-san...
It's been a while since we've all gathered together.
They are...
They are just swallowing us up.
Well...
Thank you very much for today.
Really...
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
This Christmas...
I'm so happy that we're reunited.
I'm so happy.
It's great to see you all again.
This summer has been with us all the time.
This summer, in 2020.
I hope we can go on another trip like this.
Yeah!
Right?
Shoji-san...
The lead...
The lead is...
Narita Tomo Shibu-san.
There are three of us.
Talk to him.
But, I think Hideki wants to hear your voice today.
I want to hear Hideki's voice!
It's okay.
You can talk to him.
Well, as I always say...
We've been together for the winter.
Everyone...
You're so powerful.
So powerful.
I feel so relieved...
To have you here.
Koyama-san, you were jumping around.
Stop the season in the sun
Yeah.
I was worried about my knee.
Your knee was hurting.
It's getting better.
Please don't break it.
I was surprised.
We prepared matching outfits.
I see.
We've been doing this for a long time.
It's the first time we've been wearing matching outfits.
Can the four of you line up?
Cool.
I'll feel this in the Sports History tomorrow.
It's the first time we're wearing matching outfits.
So, like this...
Are you going to get a little more excited?
Are you going to get a little more excited with rock music?
Rock music.
Yokohama!
I want to hear your voices!
Can you let me hear your voices?
Third floor!
It's about the third floor.
It's about the second floor!
And the stand!
The Show Man
Arena!
Let me hear your voices!
The members, follow me!
Let's go!
Soiya! Soiya! Soiya!
Let's go with the fast one.
Yokohama Dasogare!
Yokohama Kinbay!
Yokohama Chuka-gai!
I like rock music.
I like Noel Shoji.
I like Naritomo.
One, one, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, show me
One, two, three, four
The Show Man
That day's guitar was a blast
I played it all day until morning
I thought I could change the world that this guy had
But I couldn't sleep because I was so excited
The walls of words are also in one go
It's a magic that can surpass everything
I shout out with my voice hoarse
When I play the guitar with my voice hoarse
That's the world's best friend
I love you rock and roll
I'm in love with you
Ever since that day
I love you rock and roll
From now on, I'm all in one
Let me be your guide
Our love words
I love you rock and roll
Until I die, rock and roll
From now on, I'm all in one
I love you rock and roll
Let me be your guide
Our love words
I love you rock and roll
Until I die, rock and roll
It's not over yet
Let's go break rock and roll
The band starts off in promote
I love you yakohama
I'm in love with you
Ever since that day
I love you yakohama
From now on, I'm all in one
I love you Yokohama
Let me be absorbed
Our love words
I love you Rock'n'Roll
Until death, Rock'n'roll
I love you Rock'n'roll
Yokohama
Oh yes
Yes
I love you Rock'n'roll
The coffee is in the coffee shop
The Show Man
Do you want a point?
Was it okay?
I noticed that this group
Is full of points
I have to stop
I treat them like angels
I don't want to do anything different from everyone
It's better to be carried away by the long things
Yokohama
Give me a point
That's the spirit
Give me more
But I don't want to do anything different from everyone
Give me a point
Even if you throw gasoline
Even if you ride a plane
You will be chased by a pile of coins
If it's a chance, for the sake of the world
Let's find something we can do
Give me more
Give me a point
That's the spirit
Give me more
Let's save a lot of points
Use all the points
Thank you, thank you
Go go go
You're going to move
Let's go! That's the way to go!
Let's use more points!
Let's use up all the points
Come on!
Let's raise it! Let's raise it!
Yokohama!
Ice Shabu Shabu!
Oh my God! Aoi Yamahideki is coming!
Let's go!
Go, Wai Yatou!
Thank you!
Thank you for the encore!
Actually, during this Naritoma tour,
both me and the boys debuted in 1988.
About 20 years ago, the group sound boom was going on.
We thought that was cool,
so we were doing a medley during the Naritoma tour.
So today, can we do rock-on?
Rock-on and Naritoma, GS Medley DD!
@ YOKOHAMA BUNTAI
Today is Christmas!
On this special day,
we have a special guest!
Are you ready?
We have a big respect for
Mr. Entertainment,
Sakai Masaki!
He's a great singer!
Everybody, let's go!
See you later!
Let's go!
One, two, three, four!
Awesome!
Beautiful!
Cool all
Hey!
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba
Love is good, ba-ba-ba
It's a two-way road, ba-ba-ba
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba
Hey!
A bruised face, ba-ba-ba
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba
I can't stand him
I'm a naughty boy
Oh, boy
Bam, bam, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap
I'm a naughty boy
Bam, bam, bap
Bam, bam, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap
Bam, bam, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
《Boku no Kokoro》
あの時君は若かった
わかって欲しい　僕の心を
小さな心を　苦しめた
僕をうらまずに　いておくれ
それでも君が　望むなら
僕は待ってる　いつまでも
きっとわかって　もらえる日まで
《Boku no Kokoro》
あの時僕も　若かった
ごめんね　君を困らせちゃって
僕の心も　苦しいんだ
僕を許して　欲しいんだ
それでも君が　望むなら
僕は待ってる　いつまでも
きっとわかって　もらえる日まで
いつまでも
《Boku no Kokoro》
それでは10分間の休憩に入ります
えーみなさん
今日はこのステージに
サプライズゲストとして出演できたことを
一番嬉しく思うのと
こんな素晴らしいお客様の前で歌えるという喜びと
一番サプライズしてるのは私自身だったと
いうくらい幸せな気持ちでいっぱいでございます ありがとうございます
嬉しいです
こんな皆さんがあの赤いユリフォンを着てね
出てきてくれる私のことを歓迎してくださって 印だと思いますけど
私こんな赤いの着たのはあの
歓歴のちゃんちゃん子以来でございます
ありがとうございますですけどね
随分前に来ましたけど
こうしてまたこの赤いこれはミリタリー ルックでございますね
あのスパイラーズ時代ってもう今から60年ぐらい前に
私がまだ皆さん生まれる前だと思いますが
その頃にグループを作っておりまして
そのグループはもうこんな人気じゃなかったもっとすごかった
いやいやいや
今日のお客様の本当にこの熱気
やっぱりステージというのは半分はお客さんが作ってくれるもんだな
そういう感じをしました今日
素晴らしい
僕はこのグループをそんなに近くで見ることは今までなかったんですけど
だからグループがあるということは知ってましたけど
一つの塊として見てましたから
あの分からなかったよく分からなかった
そうしたらこの前実は武道館のファイナル
あの各種をで参って
最後に外線といいますかステージとございました
あの武道館のステージ
あれを私初めて見させていただいたの
そう素晴らしかった
そん時ちょっと来てた人ちょっと手上げ
あいたね
2階だよね
2階にいらっしゃったね
だからもうあの時のこのグループ
ソーシャルクラブ
今まで名前も違う感じで僕覚えちゃってて
ロックオンじゃなくてロックダウン
ソーシャルロックダウン
ロックオンだよね
そういう素晴らしいグループが
それで僕一番思ったのはあの時の
このサウンドと日本語の歌詞が
ものすごくうまくマッチしてるのを聞いて
素晴らしいなというふうに思いました
なかなかいないですよこういうグループは
皆さん
本当にこういうグループがもう本当に
皆さん欲しいんだけど頑張って
やってる姿を見たら僕はもう本当に
感激するしかなかったなというのもあります
今日もまた素晴らしいお客さんでありがとうございます
嬉しい嬉しい嬉しい
ありがとうございます
全てロックオンの曲は吉田さんが
曲をね吉田さんが書いて作ってくれて
そうよそうよそうよ
だからその前に皆さんの僕は名前も
分かってたんだ
ちゃんと覚えたよ
なりたくんでしょ
前田くんでしょ
高橋くんでしょ
青山くんでしょ
岡本くんでしょ
わかってますよ
それで
お名前なんておっしゃいますか
絶対そう落とすと思う
絶対来る来ると思いながらドキドキします
知ってますよ知ってますよ
彼がいろんな曲を作ってくれて
皆さんに提供することもあるし
また他のアーティストに提供することもあるし
だからある意味でもこの
海の親の一人であるという風に言っていいと思いますね
素晴らしい
で
岡本くんなんだっけ話としては
なんでしたっけ
もうちょっと地方が入っている
先生
あの何ですか
あれなんですよ
曲を作っていただけたの
もう言っていいんですか
ありがとうございます
あのですねまず
8月ぐらいに坂井さんとお会いしたんです僕
それでね
私は
スパイダーズつまり音楽からこの世界に入って
やっぱり最後やっぱり音楽に戻りたいっていう
熱いその思いをそこで
もう最後になっちゃうんですか
いやいや
まあ音楽に戻りたいっていう
最後にっていうのがちょっと余計だったんじゃん
今生放送ここだけカットでお願いします
なんかもうもうちょっとで
何か一応みたいじゃないですか
まあ言ってもいいっても
健一くん余計なこと言わないと
言わないとしてはあるんだけどさ
いつまでも
でもその思いはすごくあったんですよ
そうなんですそれでちょっとこの思いで
メンバーにもこの話をして
なんと坂井さんとロックオンで新曲作りました
しかも来年2025年1月22日に配信します
まだどんな曲が出てくるか
もう一度
まだどんな曲か何も知らないんです
すいませんがこれCDとか出さないんですか
CD欲しいですよね
配信ってのが私なんかの年代になると
迷わないで
できれば毎週で行ってほしいんですけど
その曲まだもちろんのまで演奏したことないんですけども
今日本邦初公開しても
いいですか
聞きたい?
ホント?
では本邦初公開
坂井正明&ロックオンソーシャルクラブで
プンスカピン！
給料あがんない
ローンが終わんない
プンスカピン！
深い朝がない
飲みにもいけやしない
プンスカピン！
お願い、神様
オイラを元気にしておくれ
ブンシカピーン ブンシカピーン ブンシカピーン ベペンベー
ブンシカピーン ベペンベー ブンシカピーン ベペンベー
おー 凍ってきゃうぞー
ネットでスマッション
出会いもスマッション
プンスカピン！
AI 流行っちゃう
仕事も奪っちゃう
プンスカピン！
進化か　退化か
オイラの居場所が見つからねぇ
ブンシカピーン ベペンベー ブンシカピーン ベペンベー
AI 流行っちゃう
ブンシカピーン ベペンベー ベペンベー ベペンベー
お願い、神様
オイラを元気にしておくれ
ブンシカ ベペンベー ブンシカ ベペンベー ベペンベー
「もう、笑っちゃうぞ」
プンスカピン！ピン！
08. BIG BAND BEAT
We're just a BING BING BING
You can answer this question with your free will, but if possible, please make me a member.
Thing yoyog
I don't think I need this group.
I don't need it.
I think so.
If you're a judge,
I'll ask you if you're okay with the recording of Masaaki Sakai.
If you think it's okay, please tell me.
You know  偽りを
Please do it well.
This is the last song.
Sakai wrote another song.
Anyway, every generation knows Sakai.
For example, we are the time and the best.
You know  偽りを
I think he's a showman.
That's a good word.
It's close to the word, but it's one of the words we value.
I asked Sakai to write the song, The Showman.
It's a very good song.
It's a very ballad-like song.
Please prepare a handkerchief.
I'll sing one song and see if I can fit in the recording.
I made a uniform.
It's a waste to throw it away.
It's handmade.
So I'll sing the last song and then I'll go to the trial.
Thank you.
So, as I introduced earlier,
This is my last song.
Please listen to the song, The Showman.
I've been through many times.
And today someone is calling.
It's about time.
When I realized,
Many friends have left.
And now someone is calling.
It's about time.
Sometimes I try to make someone laugh.
Sometimes I make someone surprised.
And then the showman melts into the sky like a soap bubble.
The bell rings in the evening.
I'm going to sing tonight.
It's about time.
Sometimes I fall in love with someone.
Sometimes I say goodbye to someone.
But the showman's singing continues until the curtain goes down.
The bell rings in the evening.
I'm going to sing tonight.
It's about time.
Thank you.
Now, let me announce the results of the trial.
I, Sakaiya Sawaki, will join the Rock On Social Club.
This is a very promising future for this group.
If you think so, please raise your hand.
I'm sorry, but you shouldn't raise your hand.
If you raise your hand, I'll be excited.
So please lower your hand.
I'll ask you again.
I'll join the Rock On Social Club.
Thank you.
I'll cheer for you from the outside.
The winner is Sakai Masaki.
Thank you.
I don't think there's an encore.
And tonight's special guest, from the Rock On Social Club,
Keiichi Okamoto, Kazeya Takahashi, and Koyo Maeda.
Thank you.
Give them a big hand.
Thank you very much.
Did you enjoy Yokohama?
The title of this album, Fantasia,
is a very chorus-like phrase.
Life is like Fantasy
But it's also like a dream.
That's what life is like.
And this concert is also a reality.
But tomorrow, it will be like magic.
Our Fantasia tour will soon be over.
We'll continue to make music so that we can meet you again tomorrow.
Thank you again.
I'm Tomas Simpson.
Thank you.
Stop the season in the sun
there's a saying that our imagination might make someone in the future smile.
Yes, as long as we imagine, we can create any future.
So let's imagine great things in 2025, and make it a great 2025.
Thank you.
Today is December 25, Christmas.
So I'd like to give you a present from Naritoma.
Snow White
I can see it clearly
It's not because I'm crying
It's because I'm cold
While you're crying in your white clothes
I'll spread my hands in the winter sky
I knew it before I was born
It wasn't a bad song
It was destiny
Next winter, too, let's see this snow together
Oh
@ YOKOHAMA BUNTAI
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Since everyone was born
I'm a fairy tale hero
Meeting and parting repeatedly
Eventually I'll get old and return to heaven
This world may be a illusion
We keep running
Life is like Fantasy
I'm going to live while watching the dream of just one moment
Our imagination will someday change the future
Stop the season in the sun
Applaud and praise us
This world may be a illusion
We keep running
Life is like Fantasy
I'm going to live while watching the dream of just one moment
Our imagination will someday make someone smile
Life is like Fantasy
I'm going to live while watching the dream of just one moment
Our imagination will someday change the future
Life is like Fantasy
Thank you very much!
Merry Christmas!
I would like to call these people once again
Rock on Social Club, Takahashi, Kazuha, Maeda, Koyo, Okamoto, Kenichi!
Good job!
And...
And please welcome, with a big applause, Masaki Sakai!
Thank you!
I feel like I'm going to die
I'm going to die
This world may be a illusion
We keep running
I'm going to die
This world may be a illusion
We keep running
Thank you for watching!